hourglasscareers.com 2009-04-14

# Career Network

**Browsing our web site**

In the normal course of visiting the Career-Network web site, viewing pages, or downloading information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. We use this information to help us make the site more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.   
This information does not identify you personally. We can automatically collect and store the following types of information about your visit: 

  * Your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address. (An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you go on the Web.) 
  * The domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account) 
  * The Internet address of the Web site, if any, from which you came to our site . 
  * The date and time you arrived at our site and how long you spent visiting the site. 
  * The name and version of your computer's operating system and browser: for example, Windows 95/Netscape Navigator 4.5. (This information is supplied automatically by your computer.) 
  * The pages you visit. 

**Cookies**

Some pages on this web site employ browser session "cookies." A cookie is a small piece of data that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk to allow the server to distinguish your session from that of others while you are connected. Requests to send cookies are not designed to collect information about you, but only about your "browser session." The cookies make it easier for you to use the dynamic features of our web site. The cookies and the information about your session are automatically destroyed shortly after you close your browser. The information is not permanently stored on your computer. We do not collect personal information about you except as described above.

**Web site security**

Security is a priority at Career-Network. Appropriate measures are taken to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information about our members, providers, employers, brokers, and anyone else that may want to use our web site. 

Only authorized users are allowed to access the information. Career-Network enforces a high level of protection, i.e., 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, for securing transmissions between a user's browser and this web site. Content on this site is protected against unauthorized access.

**E-mail security**

E-mail sent over the Internet is not secure and should not be used to communicate confidential and/or health information directly to Career-Network. Please be aware that Career-Network cannot guarantee the confidentiality or security of any information you send to us over the Internet when using e-mail. Career-Network shall not be liable for any breach of confidentiality resulting from such use of e-mail via the Internet. Career-Network will not use e-mail to communicate confidential and/or health information unless the e-mail is secured in accordance with Career-Network Corporate E-Mail Policy.

**Chat, Forums, Journals and WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and** **Public Rooms**

** ** Please be aware whenever you  post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that information can be accessed by the public and can, in turn, be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by Career-Network, or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Career-Network and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may make changes to our privacy policy. If changes are made, notices will be posted on this site. Users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by all changes to the policy upon using the site after those changes have been posted.  If we used a User's personally identifiable information in a different manner from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a notification on our Web site for 30 days.
